massmirror.com 2009-07-24

# MassMirror.com - Free File Hosting And Mirroring

   **MassMirror.com Privacy Policy**

> **IP Address Logging**
>
>> Each visitor who views a web page on massmirror.com is subject to ip address collection. These ip's are used to determine if you are a new or returning visitor. Your ip is also used to track your download usage, upload usage, and page views on massmirror.com. Any personal identifiable information collected from your ip is not saved or resold by massmirror.com.
> 
>  **E-mail Address Collection**
>
>> When you submit an e-mail address to massmirror we use the e-mail address temporarily to send non spam and non advertisement based e-mail messages to inform the user of the file link they uploaded. We do not attempt to save or distribute e-mail or e-mail addresses submitted by a visitor. 
> 
> **Exceptional Disclosures**
>
>> MassMirror.com holds the right to disclose personal information about a visitor when it is deemed necessary. Examples of such disclosure are as follows: If a user uploads copy written material or content, If a user is abusing our free service, If a user has caused damages to one or more other visitors or our free service, If the government or legal body legally dictates we must disclose personal information about a specific visitor, Or one of many other situations when service is abused or interrupted due to malicious or abusive activities.
> 
>  **Use of Cookies**
>
>> MassMirror.com does not employ the use of any cookies in our service. No crumbs here.
> 
>  **File Transfer Security**
>
>> MassMirror.com does not warrant this service will be 100% accurate, however we will try our best to make it as accurate as possible. We do not warrant that your files will be saved and uploaded accurately. We will do our best to create backups of files uploaded however, due to reasons out of our control we do not guarantee files will remain on our service. MassMirror.com can not be held responsible for missing, broken, or stolen data. Use At Your Own Risk.
> 
>  **Third Party Advertising**
>
>> We use third-party software to manage and maintain our ad serving space on MassMirror.com. These companys may track your personal information differently then we do. This information may include your phone number, e-mail address, home address, zip code, and location to name a few. If you are curious about the information these company's collect, please visit their privacy policy statement on their website.
> 
>  **Third Party Cookies**
>
>> Advertisers may use cookies to track your browsing history and information. Please be aware that MassMirror.com is not responsible for these third party cookies or their use.
> 
> Effective Date: May 20, 2007
